ezytred.com 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Online Fashion Clothing Wholesale : Ezytred Malaysia

The Privacy Policy applies when you visit www.ezytred.com and/or using the products and services on the site. Our Privacy Policy is established in line with PDPA. We assured our customers that the personal data collected herein will strictly be used in our normal course of business with our customers.

**Use of Personal Data**

In providing your personal data, we will use your data for the following purposes.

  * To process your online order and delivery.
  * To send you notifications on any matter related to your order, delivery and products.
  * To send you from time to time (by email) about our products, services and details of promotion. You may unsubscribe the newsletter if you do not wish to be contacted for these purposes. 
  * To verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you may make online. Payments that you make through our website will be processed by 3rd parties’ payment gateway such as Ipay88, e-GHL and etc.

The personal information we collect may include your:

  * Name
  * Telephone Number
  * Mobile Number
  * Delivery Address
  * Billing Address
  * Email Address

We will assume that any personal data given by you is accurate, complete, protected and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update your personal data, you may edit your information online, or contact us by email or phone.

**Data Disclosure**

We will not pass on your personal data to any third parties for marketing purposes other than for the purpose in conducting the normal intended business processes. Data that is forwarded to third parties such as shipping agents or payment agents will only use in connection with the delivery of goods or payments. Apart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information might be disclosed in certain situations where we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure.

**Security**

In order to protect your personal data submitted through our site from loss and unauthorized access, we do continually adapt our security measures in line with current technologies and our systems. Besides, our employees who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us.

**Cookies**

Cookies are data that is saved during subsequent visits to the site that can be retrieved from your computer or mobile device. We used third-party cookies to collect statistics from analytics and advertising party such as Google Analytics, Google Adwords. If you do not want your personal data to be collected through the use of Cookies, you may do the necessary setting for Cookie feature at the web browser. This data may include:

  * Your computer's IP address
  * The pages within Ezytred that you visited
  * The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the rights to amend the Privacy Policy statement at any time. You may review our Privacy Policy statement from time to time to keep you updated on the policy change. 

**Copyright**

The content of the site is copyright- protected and is the property of AppAsia Mall Sdn Bhd.
